Hey everyone, Prepare to be amazed by these incredible
facts about Japan. Japan is made up of over 6,800
islands. Most are uninhabited, but Honshu,
Hokkaido, Kyushu and shikoku are the four
largest. There are more than 5.5 million vending
machines in Japan offering everything from drinks and snacks
to hot meals and even umbrellas. The Japanese eat
an average of 80 pounds of seafood per year. The country
is known for its high consumption and appreciation of the
sea's bounty. Square watermelons are a real thing in Japan.
Farmers grow them in boxes to make them easier to stack and
ship. Sleeping on the job is acceptable
in Japan. Inemuri is a widespread practice that means
present while sleeping and shows dedication to work.
Mind blown, right? Which of these facts surprised you the most?
Let me know in the comments if you enjoy facts like this,
hit that like button and share this video with your friends.
Want more amazing facts? Follow for more daily
doses of knowledge.